DMITRY ISACHENKO

CIVIL ENGINEER









LINKS

Quiz on pure js with server requests:

https://dmis0474.github.io/quiz-with -API_only_public/

Layout with adaptive:

https://dmis0474.github.io/Private-je t_only_public/

Home page layout with adaptive and sliders on pure js;:

https://dmis0474.github.io/NFT-mar ket-place_only-public/

ToDo app on React:

https://github.com/Dmis0474/To-do -list-APP.git

ToDo app on React with state manager Redu:

Card game on React (educational project for understanding technologies):

Game on React (educational project for understanding technologies):

http://https://github.com/Dmis047 4/snake-game

LANGUAGES

English

My curren stack: REACT, REDUX, JS, HTML, CSS. Also used: GULP, Git, SCSS, Bootstrap.

Currently i'm studying react/redux with the guidance of an experienced mentor. There are examples of my works in portfolio. I am interested in algorithmic and logical tasks.

I am experienced in teamwork and have good communicative skills. I have worked as a civil engineer for 6 years constructing bridges and petrol stations. On my previous work place did my own projects for two years, which were finished successfully and in time.

My level of English is upper Intermediate(B2) and i'm improving it with tutor.

I am ready to solve new, difficult and interesting tasks. I am ready to be a part of big or small friendly work team to get experience and knowledge and share them.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Alumtek

Sep 2020 - Mar 2022 Rostov-na-Donu

CIVIL ENGINEER

Constructing petrol stations

ZMK MOST

Feb 2020 - Aug 2022 Omsk

CIVIL ENGINEER

Constructing bridges

ONIIP Omsk

Nov 2016 - Feb 2020 Omsk

CIVIL ENGINEER

Civil Engineer

EDUCATION

Omsk State

Technical University

2016

MASTER

Omsk

BrainsCloud courses

2022

BrainsCloud courses

SKILLS

 JavaScript, HTML & CSS, React, Redux, Git, Gulp

HOBBIES

• My Hobbies Are: -Reading Fiction And Nonfiction Literature; -Tennis (I'm Quite Good As Amateur); -CrossFit/Jogging; -Board Games.